[
    {
        "question": "What is the world's largest postal network?",
        "choices": [
            "The United States",
            "India",
            "China",
            "Russia"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Approximately how many post offices are there in India?",
        "choices": [
            "15,000",
            "150,000",
            "1,500,000",
            "50,000"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is the largest producer of sugarcane in the world?",
        "choices": [
            "Brazil",
            "India",
            "China",
            "United States"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "India is the world's largest producer of which commodity?",
        "choices": [
            "Rice",
            "Wheat",
            "Dried beans",
            "Coffee"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What are some examples of dried beans that India is the largest producer of?",
        "choices": [
            "Lentils and peas",
            "Kidney beans and chickpeas",
            "Soybeans and black beans",
            "Lima beans and pinto beans"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is home to the world's largest movie industry, Bollywood?",
        "choices": [
            "United States",
            "China",
            "India",
            "Nigeria"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In which city is Bollywood based?",
        "choices": [
            "New Delhi",
            "Mumbai",
            "Kolkata",
            "Chennai"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is another name for Bollywood?",
        "choices": [
            "The City of Gold",
            "The City of Lights",
            "The City of Dreams",
            "The City of Entertainment"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the decimal system invented in India?",
        "choices": [
            "100 AD",
            "500 AD",
            "100 BC",
            "500 BC"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "The concept of '0' (zero) as a number is the invention of which nationality?",
        "choices": [
            "Greeks",
            "Romans",
            "Egyptians",
            "Indians"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    }
]